>> Jem Young: 而之前， Sam 提到了 Brotli ，所以
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And earlier,
Sam mentioned Brotli, so
我们要在服务器上做两种基本的压缩
there's two basic types of compression
we're gonna do on servers and
在缺省情况下， NGINX 是最棒的，它被称为 gzip。
the great thing is NGINX by default
has this turned on, it's called gzip.
有谁知道一般的压缩是什么 ?
Does anybody know what
compression is in general?
你的普通心理模型是什么
Like just what's your
general mental model on it?
萨姆?
Sam?
> > Sam: 这是重复，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Sam: That is do duplication, right?
> > Jem Young: 是的，是的，这是一个很好的方法。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, yeah,
that's a good way of putting it.
> > 扬声器 3: 它正在获取信息并将其放入更小的容器中。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So it's taking information
and putting it into a smaller container.
因此，它可以是有损或无损的。
So it could be lossy or lossless.
Lossy 您抛出了希望没人注意或关心的详细信息。
Lossy you throw out details that you
hope nobody will notice or care about.
无路可就像折叠降落伞一样仔细地折叠
Lossless is like folding a parachute
you fold it carefully and
你把它放到一个小容器里
you put it into a small
of container as possible.
洛西你用一把锯或剪刀把零件切开
Lossy you take a chainsaw or
scissors and you cut out parts and
但愿它还能当降落伞
hopefully it still works as a parachute.
>> Jem Young: 是的，我不喜欢
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, no I like that.
你丢了我的降落伞卡兹我就像是
You lost me a bit about
parachute cuz I was sort of like
我应该用这个来比喻吗
that's a good analogy should I use that?
但我喜欢
But I like that.
你可能都熟悉的是 MP3s
The one you're probably all
familiar with is MP3s that
是一种有损压缩的算法
is a lossy compression algorithm.
所以如果你见过 WAV 文件现在我在和自己约会
So if you've ever seen a WAV file,
now I'm dating myself,
但是 [LAUGH] WAV 文件是未修改的无损记录音频的方式
but [LAUGH] WAV files are unmodified
lossless ways of recording audio and
在拨号上网的时候，它们是巨大的。
in the days of dial-up Internet,
they were huge.
不能共享 WAV 文件，它们可以是 200，300，400，500 兆字节
You couldn't share a WAV file they could
be 200, 300, 400, 500 megabytes for
一首歌
one song.
这简直太疯狂了需要几年的时间
That's insane on dial-up
that will take years.
所以他们发明了，改变了分享的游戏是压缩的。
So they invented, what changed
the game on sharing was compression.
他们创造了一个叫做 MP3 的东西
They created something called MP3
which is MPEG layer 3 which is
电影专家组。
Motion Picture Expert Group.
我又怎么知道这些随机的事情呢 ?
Again, why do I know these random things?
没事的，但是现在你知道这些乱真的东西，所以你应该觉得
It's okay, but now you know those random
things so you should feel as bad for
我也是个书呆子
being a nerd too.
但它所做的是把所有东西都给了一个 WAV 文件
But what it did was it took
all of given a WAV file,
你的波形看起来像这样向上和向下
you have waveforms that look
like this they go up and down.
它说，你知道，人类甚至都听不到这些东西
And it said, you know,
humans can't even hear these things so
我们先把这些切掉你有个 MP3
let's just chop those out and
you have an MP3.
而这一点
And that gets,
就像 200 兆字节的文件被记录到 2 兆字节里
like what was a 200 megabyte file down to
2 megabytes which is really impressive.
压缩的艺术的一部分是知道你能做什么
And part of the art of compression
is knowing what you can take out,
就像山姆说的压缩或压缩
so like Sam was saying lossless
compression or lossy compression.
就服务器压缩来说我们在说什么
In terms of server compression
the what where doing is we're saying,
哎，这个文件说宝石，宝石，宝石，宝石，宝石，宝石，宝石，宝石。
hey, this file says gem, gem, gem,
gem, gem, gem, gem, gem, gem.
我可以通过创建一种伪编程语言来压缩它
I can compress that by just creating
a sort of pseudo programming language that
说，不要重复宝石 20 次我只会创造 20 倍的宝石
says, instead of repeating gem 20 times
I'm just gonna create gem times 20.
这样压缩的东西就像这样，这就是压缩的本质。
And that compresses things down like this
and that's the essence of compression.
所以如果你认为 1 和 0 ，如果你说下一个区块有 10 个 1 秒，
So if you think of 1s and 0s,
if you say the next block has ten 1s and
十个 0s 只向服务器发送这些指令
ten 0s just send those instructions
down to the server and
那么客户机可以解压缩或解压缩这些文件。
then the client can unpack those or
uncompress them.
这就是你的真实情况
And that's how you have really,
能卸载到这么大的东西的小载荷
really small payloads that can
unload to something that is huge.
现在有个东西叫了，这个很有趣，一个 gzip 炸弹。
Now there's something called, and
this is just interesting, a gzip bomb.
>> Jem Young: 你觉得 gzip 炸弹是什么，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: What do you think
gzip bomb does or any sort of,
你觉得 zip 炸弹会怎么做
what do you think zip bomb does?
这是在硅谷的一个季节。
This was in Silicon Valley
one of the seasons.
>> 扬声器 4: 像这里的彼得只有那么多的记忆或类似的东西
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Like here Peter only has so
much memory or something like that and
当你不压缩它的时候它就会越来越多
then when you're uncompressing
something it takes up more and
更多的记忆你的电脑已经没有了
more memory that your computer
doesn't have anymore.
是这样吗
Is that it?
之类的吗
Something like that?
>> Jem Young: 是的，你可以创造，因为在压缩中
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, you can create,
because that languagry in compressing
你的意思是我要去拿宝石那是 30 次
where you saying like, hey,
I'm gonna take gem and that's 30 times.
但如果我们创建一个自我引用循环
But what if we just created a self
referential loop that says,
这宝石是 30 倍的宝石它会被包装在 30 次的宝石上
this is gem 30 times and it unpacks to
something that says this is gem 30 times.
然后你的文件系统会爆炸
And then your file system explodes and
你可以用被称为 zip 炸弹的整个系统
you can take down entire systems
with what are known as zip bombs.
他们的工作还挺有趣的 [ LAUGH ] ，没有什么好方法去禁用它。
They still work funny enough [LAUGH]
there's not a good way to disable that.
所以，如果你在互联网上不下载随机的文件，那就是其中之一。
So it's one of the things if you're on
the Internet don't download random files.
我不知道我为什么告诉你但是 [LAUGH] 不下载随机的 zip 文件
I don't know why I'm telling you this, but
[LAUGH] don't download random zip files,
不要随意下载类似的东西因为你不知道会发生什么
don't download random things like that
because you don't know what'll happen.
在游戏转换方面，让互联网变得更快速的 NGINX
In terms of game-changers as far as making
the Internet a little bit faster NGINX
将以 gzip 的标准格式自动压缩所有内容。
will automatically compress everything
in a standard format known as gzip.
那是 GNU zip ， G-N-U ，这是我忘记的一般东西，
That's GNU zip, G-N-U that's
the general something I forget,
但 GNU 到处都是用的
but GNU is used everywhere.
但它所做的是把所有数据都压缩出来
But what it does is it compresses all this
data going out and it reads it in that
就像我们之前描述的那样，如果有大量的 1s 和
same format about just like we described
earlier how if there's a lot of 1s and
这只是用一种我们都能理解的语言重写的
0s it just rewrites that in
a language that we all understand.
最棒的是所有浏览器都是 Safari， Internet Explorer，
And what's great is all the browsers so
Safari, Internet Explorer,
三星因特网都了解如何解包一个 gzip 文件和
Samsung Internet they all understand
how to unpack a gzip file and
这就是让你的联系更快的原因
that's what makes your connection so
much faster.
事实上，让我们来看看这个
In fact, let's check this out.
我们去 MDN我最喜欢的网站
Let's go to MDN, my favorite website and
让我们看看他们在做什么
let's check out what they're doing.
转至 " 网络 " 选项卡，并在此处看到大小 ?
Go to the Network tab,
and you see the size here?
让我再大一点
Let me make that a little bigger.
>> Jem Young: 那么一般来说，如果你在看你的审查员
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So generally, if you're
looking at your inspector you're gonna
有两个大小，一个是未压缩的大小，一个是压缩大小。
have two sizes, one is the uncompressed
size and one is the compressed size.
我们看到压缩事物的力量而不是几乎
And we see the power of compressing things
in that instead of sending down a almost
300 - 千字节文件，压缩到 37 - 千字节和
300-kilobyte file that gets
compressed to 37-kilobytes and
这就是压缩的力量
that's the power of compression.
NGINX 的伟大之处
And the great thing about NGINX and
一个更强大的事物是它在飞行中做的
one of the more powerful things
is it does this on the fly.
所以如果你把这些 NGINX 的图像发送出去
So if you're sending out images things
like that NGINX will automatically gzip
如果您将其保留在缺省情况下，请将其保留。
them if you leave it on
which is on by default.
它会为这些被压缩的图像提供服务
And it'll serve these
images compressed and
当它击中客户时就会把他们解包给你
then when it hits the client
it'll unpack them for you.
这真是太酷了
And that's just something
that's really cool.
有问题吗
Yes, question?
>> Sam: 我认为 gzip 中已省略图像，因为它们已经
&gt;&gt; Sam: I thought images were omitted
from gzip because that's they're already
以压缩格式进行编码吗 ?
encoded in as compressed
to format as they can?
>> Jem Young: 是- >> 演讲者 3: 一旦他们放大-
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Once they enlarge-
>> Jem Young: 谢谢。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Thank you.
我发错话了 映像未压缩，因为映像
I misspoke.
Images are not compressed because images
缺省情况下，使用 PNG 或 JPEG 是压缩的类型，而我认为位图
by default using PNG or JPEG are already
types of compression versus I think bitmap
BMP可能是可以压缩的，因为它是未压缩的文件。
BMP, might be able to be compressed
because that is an uncompressed file.
但这就是为什么你再也看不到在网上服务的位图了
But that's why you never see bitmaps
served over the Internet anymore,
我们以前是黑暗的日子真黑暗 [ LAUGH]
we used to, those were dark days,
really dark days [LAUGH].
谢谢你提出这个问题
But thank you for bringing up that point.
是啊，我们说压缩的时候不同类型比较多
Yes, when we talk about compression
there's different types that are more
对不同格式有效。
efficient for different formats.
因此，图像更有利于压缩，因为什么是图像?
So images in particular serve well to
compression it because what is an image?
它是一系列的点，它们是特定的颜色，如果这些点只是数学。
It's a series of dots that are certain
colors and if those dots it's just math.
如果我知道我有 50 个蓝色的点或者我想说的话
And if I know I have 50 blue dots or
if I wanna represent say,
这个板的颜色都是这样压缩好的
this board right here it's all one
color this will compress really well.
所以我可以说，大小有多大 ?
So I can just say, how big is the size?
600 比 800
600 by 800 and
都是一样的颜色我可以把它压缩到一条直线上
it's all the same color I can compress
that down to one line essentially.
这就是图像压缩在 PNG 中的威力
And that's what makes image
compression really powerful in PNG but
所以你不能把它们拉上
that's why you can't gzip them.
你真的，真的想，其实就是给它加高
You can if you really, really want to,
you'll just actually add overhead to it
因为你现在在已经压缩的东西周围加了一个拉链
because you're now adding a zip around
something that's already compressed.
你要做的就是把一些不必要的指令
So what you're doing is you're adding
unnecessary instructions to something that
它什么都不会做
it's not gonna do anything.
谢谢你提出这个问题
Thank you for
bringing up that point though.
> > Jem Young: 这会是个好课，我能感受到。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: It's gonna be a good class,
I can feel it.
所以如果你想看看你的 gzip 设置
So if you wanna check out
your gzip settings and
许多其他设置可以查看您的 NGINX.com。
lots of other settings you
can look at your NGINX.com.
我们现在不打算碰它但是如果你看看
We're not gonna touch that right now,
but if you look at it,
在缺省情况下，您会看到 gzip 处于打开状态。
you'll see that gzip is on by default.
我们可以把压缩等级设定为 1 到 9
And we can set our compression levels
to 1 through 9 I believe it is,
我不会把压缩水平弄得太乱
I wouldn't mess too much
with the compression levels.
如果能达到 9 或 11 的速度很容易
It's tempting to go all the way up to 9 or
11, if it were,
如果有人能理解这个笑话的话
[LAUGH] if anybody understands that joke.
但是老实说，在此时，您正在关闭 CPU 电源，因为它需要时间
But honestly, at this point you're trading
off CPU power because it takes time to
压缩这些东西
compress these things and
通过压缩算法与您要保存的字节数进行运行。
run through the compression algorithms
versus the amount of bytes you're saving.
6 4 是一个相当不错的水平，你可以用速度来提高性能。
And 6 4 is a pretty good level where
you're trading off speed for performance.
任何更高的速度都很有诱惑力但你真的没那么多钱
Going any higher it's really tempting but
you're honestly not saving that much.
您可以对线路进行更多优化。
There's more optimizations
you can do down the line.